Lendgismo Platform Overview — one-time code handoff. Own the code forever.
Admin, Borrower, and Broker portals with RBAC and audit logging.
CSV onboarding wizard — map fields, validate, preview, and import.
Real-time banking data integration — Plaid-ready flows and account linking.
Analytics dashboards with timeframe controls synced across charts and tables.
Payments & disbursements — Stripe-ready components and API routes.
Notifications via SMS & email — Twilio/SendGrid-ready hooks and UI.
Multi-tenant architecture — strict tenant isolation, admin tools included.
Documentation & demo data — run locally in minutes and customize quickly.
Next steps — schedule your handoff and deploy in weeks, not months.
[EDIT ME] Adjust timings and lines to match your exact cut.